{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045522157","data":{"timestamp":" 947045522157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045524496","data":{"timestamp":" 947045524496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045535753","data":{"timestamp":" 947045535752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045537497","data":{"timestamp":" 947045537497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045545619","data":{"timestamp":" 947045545619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045556719","data":{"timestamp":" 947045556719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045558843","data":{"timestamp":" 947045558843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045567889","data":{"timestamp":" 947045567889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045584107","data":{"timestamp":" 947045584107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045585702","data":{"timestamp":" 947045585702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045598056","data":{"timestamp":" 947045598056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045600026","data":{"timestamp":" 947045600026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045621652","data":{"timestamp":" 947045621652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045636989","data":{"timestamp":" 947045636988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045638822","data":{"timestamp":" 947045638821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045740964","data":{"timestamp":" 947045740964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045746646","data":{"timestamp":" 947045746646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9dcba918-cba9-45a2-9155-adfd1df1ec1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045755745","data":{"timestamp":" 947045755744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" fd297d02-f43f-4b63-aaf1-f63c6f4fa58c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045759013","data":{"timestamp":" 947045759013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" fd297d02-f43f-4b63-aaf1-f63c6f4fa58c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" itakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ITAKUWA"," userResponse":" ITAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045761996","data":{"timestamp":" 947045761996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" fd297d02-f43f-4b63-aaf1-f63c6f4fa58c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045765346","data":{"timestamp":" 947045765346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" fd297d02-f43f-4b63-aaf1-f63c6f4fa58c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045768212","data":{"timestamp":" 947045768212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" fd297d02-f43f-4b63-aaf1-f63c6f4fa58c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045772012","data":{"timestamp":" 947045772012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" fd297d02-f43f-4b63-aaf1-f63c6f4fa58c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045772426","data":{"timestamp":" 947045772426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" fd297d02-f43f-4b63-aaf1-f63c6f4fa58c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" waliokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045772504","data":{"timestamp":" 947045772504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" fd297d02-f43f-4b63-aaf1-f63c6f4fa58c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045818883","data":{"timestamp":" 947045818882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" fd297d02-f43f-4b63-aaf1-f63c6f4fa58c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" waliokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045860696","data":{"timestamp":" 947045860696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" fd297d02-f43f-4b63-aaf1-f63c6f4fa58c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" waliokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045875990","data":{"timestamp":" 947045875990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huwa_huwa-waje-tele"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huwa"," userResponse":" huwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045887023","data":{"timestamp":" 947045887023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dawa_debe-yule-dawa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dawa"," userResponse":" dawa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045895558","data":{"timestamp":" 947045895558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpwa_zote-kifo-mpwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpwa"," userResponse":" mpwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045905233","data":{"timestamp":" 947045905233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_kuwa-giza-humu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045917661","data":{"timestamp":" 947045917661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_kitu-kuwa-yule"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045927314","data":{"timestamp":" 947045927314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huwa_huwa-lisa-miye"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huwa"," userResponse":" huwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045946663","data":{"timestamp":" 947045946662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_umwa_amua-choo-umwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" umwa"," userResponse":" umwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045973580","data":{"timestamp":" 947045973580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_jivu-kuwa-wale"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045983793","data":{"timestamp":" 947045983793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ziwa_tani-ziwa-kuna"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ziwa"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046007766","data":{"timestamp":" 947046007766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_pesa-kwao-kuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046013543","data":{"timestamp":" 947046013543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" f85f0840-71ed-447d-ae7b-c11503a6b379"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_pesa-kwao-kuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046028470","data":{"timestamp":" 947046028470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046028702","data":{"timestamp":" 947046028702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046029677","data":{"timestamp":" 947046029677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046030961","data":{"timestamp":" 947046030960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046033937","data":{"timestamp":" 947046033936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046034791","data":{"timestamp":" 947046034790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046035119","data":{"timestamp":" 947046035117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046036366","data":{"timestamp":" 947046036365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046039867","data":{"timestamp":" 947046039867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046040858","data":{"timestamp":" 947046040857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046041122","data":{"timestamp":" 947046041121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046042085","data":{"timestamp":" 947046042084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046045015","data":{"timestamp":" 947046045015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046046060","data":{"timestamp":" 947046046058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046046539","data":{"timestamp":" 947046046539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046051134","data":{"timestamp":" 947046051132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046051219","data":{"timestamp":" 947046051219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" be082792-4ce5-4100-ad69-66c88d714efa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046082501","data":{"timestamp":" 947046082500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 58f7b819-a5e5-4aa9-b835-f6c837b2687d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046086658","data":{"timestamp":" 947046086658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 58f7b819-a5e5-4aa9-b835-f6c837b2687d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046086755","data":{"timestamp":" 947046086755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 58f7b819-a5e5-4aa9-b835-f6c837b2687d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046115889","data":{"timestamp":" 947046115888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" b195f887-d9f3-4b1d-8c79-e06583dec6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046117015","data":{"timestamp":" 947046117014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" b195f887-d9f3-4b1d-8c79-e06583dec6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046131416","data":{"timestamp":" 947046131416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 883a0e48-01b4-479b-94eb-923174b139c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046147854","data":{"timestamp":" 947046147854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 883a0e48-01b4-479b-94eb-923174b139c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046149815","data":{"timestamp":" 947046149815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 883a0e48-01b4-479b-94eb-923174b139c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.wa.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046151001","data":{"timestamp":" 947046151001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 883a0e48-01b4-479b-94eb-923174b139c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046158951","data":{"timestamp":" 947046158951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 883a0e48-01b4-479b-94eb-923174b139c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046167234","data":{"timestamp":" 947046167234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 883a0e48-01b4-479b-94eb-923174b139c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046175003","data":{"timestamp":" 947046175002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 883a0e48-01b4-479b-94eb-923174b139c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046184782","data":{"timestamp":" 947046184782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 883a0e48-01b4-479b-94eb-923174b139c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046190852","data":{"timestamp":" 947046190851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 883a0e48-01b4-479b-94eb-923174b139c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046199035","data":{"timestamp":" 947046199035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 883a0e48-01b4-479b-94eb-923174b139c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.wa.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___wa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046212328","data":{"timestamp":" 947046212327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046235794","data":{"timestamp":" 947046235793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046237380","data":{"timestamp":" 947046237380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046243867","data":{"timestamp":" 947046243867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046245450","data":{"timestamp":" 947046245450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046250956","data":{"timestamp":" 947046250956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046252556","data":{"timestamp":" 947046252555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" machungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046257403","data":{"timestamp":" 947046257403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" machungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046258965","data":{"timestamp":" 947046258965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046263945","data":{"timestamp":" 947046263944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046265557","data":{"timestamp":" 947046265555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046406802","data":{"timestamp":" 947046406802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046408400","data":{"timestamp":" 947046408400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046423474","data":{"timestamp":" 947046423474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046425082","data":{"timestamp":" 947046425082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hewa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWA"," userResponse":" HEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046430979","data":{"timestamp":" 947046430979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hewa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046432540","data":{"timestamp":" 947046432539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWA"," userResponse":" UKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046439211","data":{"timestamp":" 947046439211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046440760","data":{"timestamp":" 947046440760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046446918","data":{"timestamp":" 947046446918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046448939","data":{"timestamp":" 947046448939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046449113","data":{"timestamp":" 947046449113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 89d04943-64a3-47bb-a6a4-9566f3e8d3c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046459802","data":{"timestamp":" 947046459802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046460030","data":{"timestamp":" 947046460030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046460994","data":{"timestamp":" 947046460994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046462267","data":{"timestamp":" 947046462267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046465258","data":{"timestamp":" 947046465258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046466102","data":{"timestamp":" 947046466102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046466415","data":{"timestamp":" 947046466415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046467659","data":{"timestamp":" 947046467658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046471250","data":{"timestamp":" 947046471250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046472239","data":{"timestamp":" 947046472239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046472500","data":{"timestamp":" 947046472499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046473442","data":{"timestamp":" 947046473442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046476267","data":{"timestamp":" 947046476267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046477300","data":{"timestamp":" 947046477300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046477772","data":{"timestamp":" 947046477772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046482334","data":{"timestamp":" 947046482334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046482443","data":{"timestamp":" 947046482443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" a227d2ff-596e-462e-bc3a-387d4d8afa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046493108","data":{"timestamp":" 947046493108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046500467","data":{"timestamp":" 947046500466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046502043","data":{"timestamp":" 947046502043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046507449","data":{"timestamp":" 947046507449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046509050","data":{"timestamp":" 947046509050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046514367","data":{"timestamp":" 947046514367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947046515924","data":{"timestamp":" 947046515924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" machungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047059225","data":{"timestamp":" 947047059225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" machungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047060840","data":{"timestamp":" 947047060839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047077344","data":{"timestamp":" 947047077343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047078995","data":{"timestamp":" 947047078995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047280294","data":{"timestamp":" 947047280293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" START_IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047333050","data":{"timestamp":" 947047333050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" START_IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047334902","data":{"timestamp":" 947047334901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047336488","data":{"timestamp":" 947047336487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947049063317","data":{"timestamp":" 947049063317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIITWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947052543431","data":{"timestamp":" 947052543431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIITWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947052545228","data":{"timestamp":" 947052545227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947052546828","data":{"timestamp":" 947052546827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hewa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWA"," userResponse":" HEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947053805468","data":{"timestamp":" 947053805468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hewa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWA"," userResponse":" HEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947053807090","data":{"timestamp":" 947053807089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWA"," userResponse":" UKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947054131465","data":{"timestamp":" 947054131464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWA"," userResponse":" UKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947054133052","data":{"timestamp":" 947054133052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947054410617","data":{"timestamp":" 947054410617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" START_MPENDWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056591507","data":{"timestamp":" 947056591506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" START_MPENDWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056592887","data":{"timestamp":" 947056592886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.wa.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056594909","data":{"timestamp":" 947056594907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056595075","data":{"timestamp":" 947056595075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 45483f12-55a9-4695-a8fe-f4c8d45ca3ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.wa.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056682235","data":{"timestamp":" 947056682235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5390b3d3-1911-4a15-a32e-b069e0ec36aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056704540","data":{"timestamp":" 947056704540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5390b3d3-1911-4a15-a32e-b069e0ec36aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056753838","data":{"timestamp":" 947056753838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5390b3d3-1911-4a15-a32e-b069e0ec36aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056761011","data":{"timestamp":" 947056761010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5390b3d3-1911-4a15-a32e-b069e0ec36aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056766935","data":{"timestamp":" 947056766935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5390b3d3-1911-4a15-a32e-b069e0ec36aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056773044","data":{"timestamp":" 947056773044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5390b3d3-1911-4a15-a32e-b069e0ec36aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056782308","data":{"timestamp":" 947056782308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5390b3d3-1911-4a15-a32e-b069e0ec36aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056788041","data":{"timestamp":" 947056788041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5390b3d3-1911-4a15-a32e-b069e0ec36aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056794017","data":{"timestamp":" 947056794017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5390b3d3-1911-4a15-a32e-b069e0ec36aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056800646","data":{"timestamp":" 947056800645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5390b3d3-1911-4a15-a32e-b069e0ec36aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056819849","data":{"timestamp":" 947056819849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" dcc12eba-3fce-40db-9803-6e33838bb9ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hewa_hizi-hewa-wote"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hewa"," userResponse":" hewa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056870282","data":{"timestamp":" 947056870282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" dcc12eba-3fce-40db-9803-6e33838bb9ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ziwa_omba-hapo-ziwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ziwa"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056936016","data":{"timestamp":" 947056936016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" dcc12eba-3fce-40db-9803-6e33838bb9ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_nije-kuwa-geni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056936976","data":{"timestamp":" 947056936976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" dcc12eba-3fce-40db-9803-6e33838bb9ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_nije-kuwa-geni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056945230","data":{"timestamp":" 947056945229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056945452","data":{"timestamp":" 947056945452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056946416","data":{"timestamp":" 947056946416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056947689","data":{"timestamp":" 947056947689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056950556","data":{"timestamp":" 947056950556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056951399","data":{"timestamp":" 947056951399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056951712","data":{"timestamp":" 947056951712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056952944","data":{"timestamp":" 947056952944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056956434","data":{"timestamp":" 947056956434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056957429","data":{"timestamp":" 947056957429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056957691","data":{"timestamp":" 947056957691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056958642","data":{"timestamp":" 947056958642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056961502","data":{"timestamp":" 947056961500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056962540","data":{"timestamp":" 947056962540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056963018","data":{"timestamp":" 947056963017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056967637","data":{"timestamp":" 947056967636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056967745","data":{"timestamp":" 947056967745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.wa.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056982440","data":{"timestamp":" 947056982440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056992080","data":{"timestamp":" 947056992080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.we.rand.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947056999562","data":{"timestamp":" 947056999562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c2a15390-b713-48fe-ba36-ff6d9b9d0934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057009230","data":{"timestamp":" 947057009230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057009459","data":{"timestamp":" 947057009459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057010431","data":{"timestamp":" 947057010431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057011713","data":{"timestamp":" 947057011712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057014661","data":{"timestamp":" 947057014660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057015516","data":{"timestamp":" 947057015516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057015832","data":{"timestamp":" 947057015831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057017084","data":{"timestamp":" 947057017083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057020714","data":{"timestamp":" 947057020713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057021716","data":{"timestamp":" 947057021716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057021978","data":{"timestamp":" 947057021978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057022929","data":{"timestamp":" 947057022928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057025866","data":{"timestamp":" 947057025865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057026913","data":{"timestamp":" 947057026912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057027409","data":{"timestamp":" 947057027409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057032007","data":{"timestamp":" 947057032006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057032138","data":{"timestamp":" 947057032138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 6fe30c18-e7b5-46bc-a80d-69e4be63188c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057047179","data":{"timestamp":" 947057047179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wewe_duni-damu-wewe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wewe"," userResponse":" wewe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057059277","data":{"timestamp":" 947057059277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yowe_yowe-nasi-wiki"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yowe"," userResponse":" yowe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057071446","data":{"timestamp":" 947057071446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yawe_yawe-umwa-wivu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yawe"," userResponse":" yawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057083455","data":{"timestamp":" 947057083455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wewe_wewe-safi-hawa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wewe"," userResponse":" wewe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057092903","data":{"timestamp":" 947057092903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kiwe_saba-kiwe-naro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kiwe"," userResponse":" kiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057109033","data":{"timestamp":" 947057109032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mawe_hiki-mawe-jike"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mawe"," userResponse":" mawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057118487","data":{"timestamp":" 947057118487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mawe_mawe-tawi-wapi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mawe"," userResponse":" mawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057127577","data":{"timestamp":" 947057127576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_niwe_ombe-humu-niwe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" niwe"," userResponse":" niwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057136268","data":{"timestamp":" 947057136268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wewe_kati-jina-wewe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wewe"," userResponse":" wewe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057146199","data":{"timestamp":" 947057146199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jiwe_jiwe-hebu-ndoo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jiwe"," userResponse":" jiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057149859","data":{"timestamp":" 947057149858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_jiwe_jiwe-hebu-ndoo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057158218","data":{"timestamp":" 947057158217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_jiwe_jiwe-hebu-ndoo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.we.show.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057164928","data":{"timestamp":" 947057164928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" c25ae080-1cb9-4a3b-8b86-ae6fa781bb6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_jiwe_jiwe-hebu-ndoo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057173460","data":{"timestamp":" 947057173459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057173686","data":{"timestamp":" 947057173686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057174649","data":{"timestamp":" 947057174648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057175922","data":{"timestamp":" 947057175922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057178821","data":{"timestamp":" 947057178821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057179665","data":{"timestamp":" 947057179665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057179978","data":{"timestamp":" 947057179978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057181211","data":{"timestamp":" 947057181211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057184713","data":{"timestamp":" 947057184713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057185698","data":{"timestamp":" 947057185697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057185951","data":{"timestamp":" 947057185951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057186894","data":{"timestamp":" 947057186894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057189742","data":{"timestamp":" 947057189742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057190780","data":{"timestamp":" 947057190780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057191257","data":{"timestamp":" 947057191257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057195816","data":{"timestamp":" 947057195816"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057195903","data":{"timestamp":" 947057195903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 9384a6d3-b962-4cb4-b938-68c53038a45e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057207028","data":{"timestamp":" 947057207028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057207251","data":{"timestamp":" 947057207251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057208214","data":{"timestamp":" 947057208214"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057209488","data":{"timestamp":" 947057209488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057212370","data":{"timestamp":" 947057212370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057213215","data":{"timestamp":" 947057213215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057213529","data":{"timestamp":" 947057213529"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057214762","data":{"timestamp":" 947057214762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057218262","data":{"timestamp":" 947057218262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057219246","data":{"timestamp":" 947057219246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057219499","data":{"timestamp":" 947057219499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057220443","data":{"timestamp":" 947057220443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057223291","data":{"timestamp":" 947057223291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057224325","data":{"timestamp":" 947057224325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057224798","data":{"timestamp":" 947057224798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057229322","data":{"timestamp":" 947057229321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057229477","data":{"timestamp":" 947057229477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 5cc752d6-590b-43fc-be6d-42669802608e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057272111","data":{"timestamp":" 947057272110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057272334","data":{"timestamp":" 947057272334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057273297","data":{"timestamp":" 947057273297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057274571","data":{"timestamp":" 947057274571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057277447","data":{"timestamp":" 947057277447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057278290","data":{"timestamp":" 947057278290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057278604","data":{"timestamp":" 947057278604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057279836","data":{"timestamp":" 947057279836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057283320","data":{"timestamp":" 947057283320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057284306","data":{"timestamp":" 947057284306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057284560","data":{"timestamp":" 947057284560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057285504","data":{"timestamp":" 947057285503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057288325","data":{"timestamp":" 947057288325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057289359","data":{"timestamp":" 947057289359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057289831","data":{"timestamp":" 947057289831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057294378","data":{"timestamp":" 947057294376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057294486","data":{"timestamp":" 947057294486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057316374","data":{"timestamp":" 947057316374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 861aa425-4f48-4117-9391-a7bf1d124ec6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057339149","data":{"timestamp":" 947057339149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 37778a47-10c4-403e-b8f6-eef8a95b0614"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947057346294","data":{"timestamp":" 947057346294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_071127"," gameId":" 37778a47-10c4-403e-b8f6-eef8a95b0614"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}